他不是真实的人 他就是一堆机器人组成的
He isn't even really a guy, he's just a‐a pile of robots.
话虽如此
It's true.
我是由数以万亿计的
I am composed of
且可以自我复制的纳米机器人构成的
a trillion microscopic, self‐replicating robots,
但我知道
but I know
所有人都需要...
that all humans require
需要...
require
在橡树大道的拐弯处安插停止标识
a stop sign at the corner of Oak and Main.
人们每次从那边开过的时候都跟赛车似的
People speed through there like they're street racing.
这样子不对 而我能帮助到大家
It's got to stop, and I can make it happen.
- 不行 什么 - 不不不不不
‐ No. What? ‐ No, no, no, no, no.
不能这样 快停止计时
I‐I‐I don't think so, stop the clock.
我们已经辩论过了 大家现在应该开始投票了
We already had the debate. Everyone has to vote right now.
你从哪里找的这身行头 脱了
Where did you get that suit? Take it off.